Mitchell Levy mitchlevy@gmail.com - (650) 302-0152

My goal is to move into the exciting, ever-changing television and film industry, with opportunities for upward mobility. In my past work experience, I've proven that my skillset includes teachability, adaptability, and being a reliable teammate. These skills, when combined with my attention to detail and my patient, empathetic approach to communication, make me the perfect candidate for your team.

Education + Certifications

UCLA School of Medicine, Prehospital Medical Center

Graduate 2014

University of Oregon

Journalism; No Degree 2002-2004

Mountain View High School

Graduate 1999-2002

North American Outdoor Leadership School

Wilderness Survival and Self-Reliance 2007

CrossFit

Level 1 Trainer

Precision Nutrition

Level 1 Nutritionist

American Heart Association

CPR for the Professional Rescuer

Professional Assoc. of Diving Instructors

Open Water SCUBA Diver

National Registry of Emergency Medical Technicians; EMT

Los Angeles County (inactive)

American Red Cross

CPR/First Aid Instructor (inactive)

FreeCodeCamp

HTML, CSS, JS Responsive Web Design Certification Program

LinkedIn Learning

PhotoShop Fundamentals

Familiarity + Skills

Microsoft Suite Google Suite; gMail

Google Suite; gMail
Adobe CC; Photoshop, Premiere Pro
After Effects, Illustrator, Acrobat
Storyboard Pro, Shotgun, Avid MC
HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python
Scheduling, Calendar Keeping
Note taking, Listening
Public Speaking, Problem Solving

Other Experiences

Swimming, Strength & Conditioning Coach

Valley Academy of Art & Science (Sept 2012 - Jan 2015)

Work Experience

July 2017 - Present

Gym Manager, Program Director, Personal Trainer

CrossFit High Voltage [Formerly Modern Viking Athletics] - Burbank, CA

Managed day-to-day operations of the 200+ member gym by organizing schedules, programs, staffing, equipment purchases, and events. Designed and deployed a highly successful on-site and online coaching program with a fully custom web app. Used organizational and progress tracking software to track improvements and trajectories of all clients. Fostered growth in clients through well-crafted programming, and patient, honest support. Helped to instruct new and experienced staff in gym operations.

January 2015 - August 2017

Emergency Medical Technician McCormick Ambulance - Torrance, CA

June 2014 - January 2015

Emergency Medical Technician MedResponse Ambulance - Van Nuys, CA

Responded quickly and safely to 911 emergencies. Worked effectively in a team environment to provide life-saving care calmly and professionally under extreme stress. Utilized a warm and friendly demeanor to empathize with patients. Adapted to challenges and grew from supervisor feedback. Awarded LA County honors for excellence in lifesaving.

March 2009 - September 2009, September 2012 - June 2014

Lifeguard Supervisor, Swim Instructor Aquatic Safety Instruction - Northridge, CA Managed acquisitions, scheduling, and training of lifeguard team. Taught instructional swim for children and adults of all developmental and skill levels. Created training seminars for non-lifeguard summer camp and school staff to cultivate a safer pool environment and to better manage emergency situations.

September 2009 - September 2012

House Manager, Recovery Coach Sober College - Woodland Hills, CA

Provided general oversight to ensure safety and well-being of clients. Managed staff roles and schedules in the recovery house. Organized school and clinical schedules for clients. Taught life skills, cooking, cleaning, budgeting, schedule keeping to house members. Tracked client progress with daily notes and maintained progress and case notes database.

June 2004 - February 2009

Teacher, Counselor, Director Eugene Family YMCA - Eugene, OR

Designed and organized summer camp and after school youth programs for at-risk kids. Led 40-student outdoor adventures and backpacking trips. Lead elementary aged afterschool classroom. Communicated and planned with teachers, students, and parents to create best environment for success.